fantasticautoinsurance.com 2016-06-19

# Privacy Policy

Please read our privacy policy carefully before using this site

This Site is primary for informational purposes, but when requesting information or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and other personally identifiable information.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Information Collection

  * We may collect basic information when registering our Site, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and other identifiable information
  * We may collect personal information that can identify you, such as your name and e-mail address, as well as other information that does not identify you.
  * We may collect and store any personal information you provide to us, such as when you contact us for help.
  * We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our Site.
  * We and our business partners, such as advertisers, may use technologies to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to other websites.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. We collect non-personal information about your use of our website through the use of cookies. The information collected by cookies allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our website. We may use cookie information to determine the popularity of certain content and how long visitors stay on the site. fantasticautoinsurance.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information in any way. 

Third Party Service Providers

In the event that we use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf, these companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gift or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. Company may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and Company subsequently acquires or uses the information provided by the third party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the you may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, Company seeks assurances from the third party that you agreed to provide and have such information acquired by Company.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with fantasticautoinsurance.com rules, regulations and policies.

Transfer of Data Abroad

If you are visiting this Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries.   
By visiting this Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers. 

Changes in Our Practices

fantasticautoinsurance.com Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time to reflect changes in our practices and Services. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Contacting our Site

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, contact us or leave messages.
